Let's see who dares kick me out
I'm carrying a Jiang heir
He's your grandson
Could you bear letting him roam the streets?
Stop pretending
At your age
how could you even get pregnant?
This is a hospital
I can't lie here
Son, I'm begging you
I'm already ruined
The Jiang family's only heir
Come out
I exposed my husband's affair
and was killed
This life
your family will pay in blood
Xiaolan, come
come wash my feet
Zhang Guifen, don't push it
Oh my
My precious son says
he wants Grandma serving him
If she doesn't serve well
he won't come out
He'll just stay in there
let's see who panics
You little cutie
Honey
Honey, calm down
Careful of the baby in her belly
If not for the child
carrying our Jiang blood
I'd have thrown you out already
Don't hurt the baby
Something's wrong
The way Jiang Chengang looked
that's not how you look at a daughter-in-law
Oh Chengang
gently now
I'm carrying your child
don't crush him